<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<topics>
  <topic>
    <id>topictrain1</id>
    <discharge_summary>09963-257487-RADIOLOGY_REPORT.doc</discharge_summary>
    <title>Crohn’s disease</title>
    <desc>What is Crohn’s disease and can it be cured?</desc>
    <narr>Documents should contain information about Crohn’s disease and its treatment. It should describe the disease and its treatment.</narr>
    <profile>We assume that this patient seeks information for himself, he is familiar with search engines. This is a newly diagnosed chronic disease. He wants to know what is Crohn’s disease.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain2</id>
    <discharge_summary>10101-012638-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Metastases of adrenals and pain and pain treatment</title>
    <desc>How painful are the growing metastases and what are the possibilities for pain treatment? </desc>
    <narr>Documents should contain information about metastases of adrenals, paindisease and pain and pain medications and possible other pain alleviation methods. It should describe the condition and possibilities of different types of pain management.</narr>
    <profile>We assume that this patient is not familiar with www and he asks his son/daughter to seek for information about the growth of metastases, their painfulness and pain treatment.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain3</id>
    <discharge_summary>19709-026760-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>radial neck fracture and healing time</title>
    <desc>How long time one has to have the splint with sling in the case of radial neck fracture?</desc>
    <narr>Documents should contain information about the healing time of radial neck fracture and how long one has to have the splint.</narr>
    <profile>We assume that this woman has been in an accident and has a lot of other more severe diagnosis at the same time only wants to know about this acute condition how long she has to have the splint with sling.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain4</id>
    <discharge_summary>21413-012450-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Cdiff</title>
    <desc>What is Cdiff, why is it so dangerous and could something have been done at an earlier stage?</desc>
    <narr>Documents should contain information about clostridium difficile and it’s seriousness and are there possible effective treatments. There should also be information about the contagiousness of the disease.</narr>
    <profile>We assume since the patient died the children want to know why this acute condition was so serious that their father died</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain5</id>
    <discharge_summary>21833-003461-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Group B streptococcus and treatment and renal</title>
    <desc>What is group b streptococcus and what kind of treatment options are there? Can it harm the renals?</desc>
    <narr>Documents should contain information about the group B streptococcus bacteria and the treatment options and also information about the bacteria in renals.</narr>
    <profile>We assume that this 35 year old woman seeks info herself for this acute condition and wants to know about the bacteria and the treatment options and how it affects the renals</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain6</id>
    <discharge_summary>08114-027513-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>MRSA and wound infection</title>
    <desc>What is MRSA infection and is it dangerous?</desc>
    <profile>This 60 year old lady has had coronary artery bypass grafting surgery and during recovery her wound has been infected. She wants to know how dangerous her infection is, where she got it and if she can be infected again with it.</profile>
    <narr>Documents should contain information about sternal wound infection by MRSA. They should describe the causes and the complications.</narr>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain7</id>
    <discharge_summary>22743-004908-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>CSF infection and medication</title>
    <desc>What is CSF infection and what kind of medications are recommended?</desc>
    <profile>Metastasic breast cancer patient with CSF infection. This nearly 60-year old woman has a severe metastasic cancer. She has had several complications and is very tired. She has a supportive family and now her husband and herself want to know more about her latest complication; a cerebro spinal fluid infection in the shunt which delivers chemotherapy to the central nervous system.</profile>
    <narr>Documents should contain information about the infection and its treatment.</narr>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain8</id>
    <discharge_summary>07726-023607-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>End stage renal disease</title>
    <desc>Is it possible that the kidneys start to work again?</desc>
    <profile>This 46-year old woman is suffering from end stage renal disease and is depressed. She has not been going to her daily dialysis and is now suffering from the consequences. She still thinks that her kidneys will start working. She has a lifestyle that is not supporting the regular lifestyle that would be necessary for her stage. Now she wants to know will she ever be cured.</profile>
    <narr>Documents should describe end stage renal disease and its care.</narr>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain9</id>
    <discharge_summary>20288-027184-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>aortic dissection</title>
    <desc>What is aortic dissection, can it come again and how serious of a disease is it?</desc>
    <profile>This 80 year old male has had several medical conditions. He has now been found with aortic dissection, and an operation has been performed to treat this. The family wants to know more about the disease and its severity.</profile>
    <narr>Documents should contain general information about aortic dissection and its severity. </narr>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain10</id>
    <discharge_summary>07352-013977-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Esophageal perforation and risk</title>
    <desc>What is esophageal perforation and can it reappear?</desc>
    <profile>This nearly 70-year old male has advanced multiple sclerosis and several other medical conditions. Previously he has had an esophageal polyp that has been removed. After removal he had a perforation and was admitted to hospital. Now his home nurse wants to know what is the risk of him getting this perforation again?</profile>
    <narr>Documents should contain general information about esophageal perforation and risks of obtaining this disorder again.</narr>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain11</id>
    <discharge_summary>00098-016139-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Hypothyreoidism</title>
    <desc>What is hypothyreoidism</desc>
    <narr>description of what type of disease hypothyreoidism is</narr>
    <profile>A forty year old woman, who seeks information about her condition</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain12</id>
    <discharge_summary>01314-028800-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Facial cuts and scar tissue</title>
    <desc>Healing of cuts and forming of scar tissue</desc>
    <narr>wounds or cuts in face and scar tissue</narr>
    <profile>A 70 year old man who wants to know about scars and how painful they are and how long time does it take for them to disappear from the face</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain13</id>
    <discharge_summary>02115-010823-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Asystolic arrest</title>
    <desc>what is asystolic arrest</desc>
    <narr>asystolic arrest and why does it cause death</narr>
    <profile>A 87 year old woman with a stroke and asystolic arrest dies and the daughter wants to know about asystolic arrest and what it means.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain14</id>
    <discharge_summary>02136-017465-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>nausea and vomiting and hematemesis</title>
    <desc>What are nausea, vomiting and hematemesis</desc>
    <narr>What is the connection with nausea, vomiting and hematemesis</narr>
    <profile>A 64-year old emigrant who is not sure what nausea, vomiting and hematemesis mean in his discharge summary</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain15</id>
    <discharge_summary>02410-026171-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Sinus tachycardia</title>
    <desc>What is Sinus tachycardia</desc>
    <narr>Sinus tachycardia</narr>
    <profile>A 71-year old man who has had problems with his heart and has now first time symptoms of Sinus tachycardia and wants to know more about that</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain16</id>
    <discharge_summary>02652-006395-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Chills and gallstones</title>
    <desc>What is the connection between chills and gallstones</desc>
    <narr>a description of gallstones and symptoms in connection with them.</narr>
    <profile>A 79-year old gentleman who wants to know why doctor is asking about chills in connection with gallstones. He seeks info by himself.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain17</id>
    <discharge_summary>03273-009330-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>seizures and alcohol withdrawal syndrome</title>
    <desc>Why does alcohol withdrawal cause seizures</desc>
    <narr>seizures and alcohol withdrawal syndrome</narr>
    <profile>A 47-year old male who visits a substance abuse consultant and discusses alcohol withdrawal symptoms with the consultant. Together they seek info from the internet.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain18</id>
    <discharge_summary>04266-000520-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Acidosis and metastasic adeno carcinoma</title>
    <desc>what is the connection between acidosis and metastasic adeno carcinoma</desc>
    <narr>Acidosis and metastasic adeno carcinoma</narr>
    <profile>A 76-year old man who dies from metastatic adeno carcinoma. The family is wondering about the asidocis and its connection with carcinoma.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain19</id>
    <discharge_summary>04269-027967-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>vegetation and pulmonic valve</title>
    <desc>why is the vegetation condition of pulmonic valve in the interest of the physician</desc>
    <narr>vegetation in pulmonic valves</narr>
    <profile>A 39-year old Patient wants to know what the physician means with vegetation suspected in pulmonic valves</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain20</id>
    <discharge_summary>07352-013977-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>dysplasia and multiple sclerosis</title>
    <desc>is there a connection between multiple sclerosis and dysplasia in oesophagus</desc>
    <narr>dysplasia in oesophagus and multiple sclerosis</narr>
    <profile>A 67-year old male who has a long history of Multiple Sclerosis and wants to know what is dysplasia and is it common when one has Multiple sclerosis</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain21</id>
    <discharge_summary>07514-025655-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>chest pain and liver transplantation</title>
    <desc>can chest pain hinder the transplantation of liver</desc>
    <narr>liver transplantation and chest pain</narr>
    <profile>A 46-year-old male who is waiting for liver transplantation and wants to know why the doctor was interested in his chest pain</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain22</id>
    <discharge_summary>07726-023607-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>clots in jugular and HIV</title>
    <desc>is clots in jugular in connection with HIV</desc>
    <narr>clots in jugular and HIV</narr>
    <profile>The 46-year old woman with end stage renal disease and polysubstance abuse is depressed and wants to find out about her chance of having HIV.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain23</id>
    <discharge_summary>08114-027513-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>hepatosplenomegaly</title>
    <desc>what is hepatosplenomegaly</desc>
    <narr>hepatopsplenomegaly</narr>
    <profile>A 60-year old female with previous history of a heart operation and has now severe infection. However in her discharge summary the doctor has ruled out hepatosplenomegaly and now she wants to know what that is.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain24</id>
    <discharge_summary>08703-021487-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>frothy sputum and care</title>
    <desc>how to avoid frothy sputum</desc>
    <narr>frothy sputum and how to avoid and care for this condition</narr>
    <profile>A 43-year old male with down Syndrome lives in an extended care facility. The personnel wants to know if they can avoid frothy sputum in connection with the patient's chronic aspiration and status post laryngectomy</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain25</id>
    <discharge_summary>08951-002958-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>shortness of breath and swelling</title>
    <desc>is shortness of breath in connection with swelling</desc>
    <narr>shortness of breath and swelling</narr>
    <profile>A 71-year old male who has had problems with his heart and has now shortness of breath and swelling. He wants to know if these two symptoms are connected</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain26</id>
    <discharge_summary>00211-027889-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Coronary artery disease.</title>
    <desc>What does coronary artery disease mean? </desc>
    <narr>The documents should contain basic information about coronary artery disease and its care.</narr>
    <profile>This positive 83 year old woman has had problems with her heart with increased shortness of breath for a while. She has now received a diagnosis for these problems having visited a doctor. She and her daughter are seeking information from the internet related to the condition she has been diagnosed with. They have no knowledge about the disease.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain27</id>
    <discharge_summary>01234-029456-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Sepsis</title>
    <desc>Could sepsis be the cause of death?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about sepsis in general and its possible consequences</narr>
    <profile>The patient was an 83 year-old lady who died after sepsis. Her daughter wants to know if sepsis  is the possible cause of her death. She does not know what sepsis means.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain28</id>
    <discharge_summary>01314-028800-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>L hemopneumothorax</title>
    <desc>What are the late complications of hemopneumothorax?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about the late complications of  hemopneumothorax. </narr>
    <profile>70 year old male had driven a car without safety belt and ended up in an accident. He has multiple fractures on his chest and elsewhere. His relatives want to know how they should take care of him at home. They are advised to check regularly if he has chest pain, shortness of breath, severe nausea or vomiting, high fever, or weakness. They want to know why.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain29</id>
    <discharge_summary>02115-010823-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Anoxic brain injury</title>
    <desc>Can one experience pain if there is a severe brain injury?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about brain injury and pain.</narr>
    <profile>The daughter of this now dead 87 year old woman wants to know if it was possible for her mother to have unnoticed pain with the severe brain injury that she had in her last days. </profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain30</id>
    <discharge_summary>02136-017465-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Upper gastrointestinal bleed</title>
    <desc>What are the possible causes of gastrointestinal bleeding?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about causes of gastrointestinal bleeding.</narr>
    <profile>This male patient is familiar with most of his diseases but now wants to know what could have caused his gastrointestinal bleeding. He did not get a clear answer from the doctor and his discharge summary did not reveal the answer either. </profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain31</id>
    <discharge_summary>02410-026171-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Aortic stenosis</title>
    <desc>What is aortic stenosis and how is it treated?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about aortic stenosis and its treatment options.</narr>
    <profile>71 year old man has had aortic stenosis before and is familiar with the disease. He knows quite a lot about his disease but since it is a while since his previous operation he wants to update his knowledge on the disease and its treatment.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain32</id>
    <discharge_summary>02652-006395-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Dropped gallstone abscess, right flank</title>
    <desc>How can one get a dropped gallstone abscess and are they common?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about dropped gallstones, their abscesses, how frequent they are and what causes them.</narr>
    <profile>This patient is a relatively healthy elderly man. He is curious to know more about gallstones and especially how they can get abscesses and become dropped.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain33</id>
    <discharge_summary>03273-009330-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Alcohol withdrawal seizures</title>
    <desc>How dangerous are alcohol withdrawal seizures?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about alcohol withdrawal seizures and their consequences.</narr>
    <profile>This 47 year old man has a long history of alcohol and other substance abuse. His sister wants to explain to their parents the type of problem alcohol withdrawal seizures is and its consequences </profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain34</id>
    <discharge_summary>04269-027967-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Right upper lobe pneumonia with cavitary lesion </title>
    <desc>What does cavitary lesion mean in connection with upper lobe pneumonia?</desc>
    <narr>This document should contain inforamtion about upper loab pneumonia and cavitary lesions</narr>
    <profile>This 39 year old male has been mostly healthy but now after aspiration has developed pneumonia. He wants to know more about it, since it has made him feel very tired and uncomfortable.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain35</id>
    <discharge_summary>04303-005081-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Traumatic brain injury, status post fall</title>
    <desc>What are the possible consequences of brain injury?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about brain injury and its possible consequences</narr>
    <profile>The patient has had brain injury following a fall. He and his children want to know what they should be aware of now that the patient is being discharged from hospital and there is still a danger of bleeding.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain36</id>
    <discharge_summary>07429-001857-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>aspiration pneumonia due to misplacement of dobhoff tube</title>
    <desc>What is a dobhoff tube and why has it caused pneumonia</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about a dobhoff tube and consequences of misplacement.</narr>
    <profile>This elderly lady has been in a bad car accident. She has needed a tube for feeding. The tube has accidentally been placed to her lung instead of stomach. It has caused pneumonia. The family wants to know if this is a common problem or rather a rare accident.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain37</id>
    <discharge_summary>07514-025655-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>hepatic encephalopathy</title>
    <desc>What is hepatic encephalopathy and why does it cause confusion?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about hepatic encephalopathy and its consequences</narr>
    <profile>The patient has a history of C-hepatitis and now suffers from hepatic encephalopathy. Patient and wife want to know more about this scary problem and how dangerous it really is.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain38</id>
    <discharge_summary>08703-021487-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Status post narrow field laryngectomy</title>
    <desc>What is narrow field laryngectomy?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about narrow field laryngectomy. </narr>
    <profile>This young man with downs syndrome has had chronic aspiration for a long time and his larynx has now been operated on. The patients family wants to know more about the procedure that was conducted.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain39</id>
    <discharge_summary>09337-018472-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Myocardial infarction</title>
    <desc>What is myocardial infarction?</desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about myocardial infarction.</narr>
    <profile>This elderly lady has had her first myocardial infarction and she and her family want to know more about the disease since no one in her close family has ever had heart diseases.</profile>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>topictrain40</id>
    <discharge_summary>10101-012638-DISCHARGE_SUMMARY.txt</discharge_summary>
    <title>Non small cell lung cancer</title>
    <desc>Is lung cancer hereditary? </desc>
    <narr>The document should contain information about different types of lung cancer and how likely it is that it runs in the family.</narr>
    <profile>The 74 year old male patient dies from lung cancer and his children want to know if it is likely that they will also get lung cancer.</profile>
  </topic>
</topics>
